{"sid": "476JBFDP1NQM_main", "calc_equals_delay": 0, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 9, "start_time": 348251, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 348251, "question": "98+744", "correct_answer": 842, "events": [["submit", 354412]], "time_left_end": "294", "answered_time": 354412, "user_answer": "742", "user_correct": "False", "score": "-1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "294", "question_time_start": 354412, "question": "88+73+24+53", "correct_answer": 238, "events": [["calc_8", 358157], ["calc_8", 358332], ["calc_+", 358807], ["calc_7", 359271], ["calc_3", 359816], ["calc_+", 360365], ["calc_2", 360819], ["calc_4", 361312], ["calc_+", 361719], ["calc_5", 362106], ["calc_3", 362341], ["calc_=", 362645], ["submit", 365880]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "283", "answered_time": 365880, "user_answer": "238", "user_correct": "True", "score": "0"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "283", "question_time_start": 365881, "question": "7+17+17", "correct_answer": 41, "events": [["submit", 368166]], "time_left_end": "281", "answered_time": 368166, "user_answer": "41", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "281", "question_time_start": 368166, "question": "24+179", "correct_answer": 203, "events": [["submit", 371819]], "time_left_end": "277", "answered_time": 371819, "user_answer": "203", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "277", "question_time_start": 371820, "question": "33+86+14+77", "correct_answer": 210, "events": [["calc_3", 375681], ["calc_3", 375807], ["calc_+", 376106], ["calc_8", 376846], ["calc_6", 377096], ["calc_+", 377625], ["calc_1", 377989], ["calc_4", 378200], ["calc_+", 378625], ["calc_7", 379133], ["calc_7", 379258], ["calc_=", 379683], ["submit", 381803]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "267", "answered_time": 381803, "user_answer": "210", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "267", "question_time_start": 381804, "question": "47+69+759", "correct_answer": 875, "events": [["calc_1", 396553], ["calc_1", 396667], ["calc_6", 397040], ["calc_+", 397432], ["calc_7", 397968], ["calc_5", 398293], ["calc_9", 398786], ["calc_=", 399202], ["submit", 402189]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "247", "answered_time": 402189, "user_answer": "875", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "247", "question_time_start": 402190, "question": "9+3+7+44", "correct_answer": 63, "events": [["submit", 406803]], "time_left_end": "242", "answered_time": 406803, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "242", "question_time_start": 406804, "question": "68+818", "correct_answer": 886, "events": [["submit", 416387]], "time_left_end": "232", "answered_time": 416387, "user_answer": "686", "user_correct": "False", "score": "4"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "232", "question_time_start": 416388, "question": "3+37+76", "correct_answer": 116, "events": [["submit", 419552]], "time_left_end": "229", "answered_time": 419552, "user_answer": "116", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "229", "question_time_start": 419553, "question": "9+9+4+87", "correct_answer": 109, "events": [["submit", 425430]], "time_left_end": "223", "answered_time": 425430, "user_answer": "109", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 9, "start_time": 425430, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "223", "question_time_start": 425430, "question": "86+338", "correct_answer": 424, "events": [["submit", 438723]], "time_left_end": "210", "answered_time": 438723, "user_answer": "424", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "210", "question_time_start": 438723, "question": "4+46+18", "correct_answer": 68, "events": [["submit", 440831]], "time_left_end": "208", "answered_time": 440831, "user_answer": "68", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "208", "question_time_start": 440832, "question": "98+496", "correct_answer": 594, "events": [["submit", 450023]], "time_left_end": "199", "answered_time": 450023, "user_answer": "594", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "199", "question_time_start": 450024, "question": "3+99+79", "correct_answer": 181, "events": [["submit", 457723]], "time_left_end": "191", "answered_time": 457723, "user_answer": "181", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "191", "question_time_start": 457724, "question": "47+57+84+17", "correct_answer": 205, "events": [["calc_4", 461275], ["calc_7", 461546], ["calc_+", 462032], ["calc_5", 462550], ["calc_7", 462797], ["calc_+", 463292], ["calc_8", 463894], ["calc_4", 464224], ["calc_+", 464774], ["calc_1", 465721], ["calc_7", 466149], ["calc_=", 466610], ["submit", 468929]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "180", "answered_time": 468929, "user_answer": "205", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "180", "question_time_start": 468930, "question": "4+6+3+49", "correct_answer": 62, "events": [["submit", 472650]], "time_left_end": "176", "answered_time": 472650, "user_answer": "62", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "176", "question_time_start": 472651, "question": "29+499", "correct_answer": 528, "events": [["submit", 476315]], "time_left_end": "172", "answered_time": 476315, "user_answer": "528", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "172", "question_time_start": 476316, "question": "26+19+14+38", "correct_answer": 97, "events": [["submit", 485654]], "time_left_end": "163", "answered_time": 485654, "user_answer": "97", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "163", "question_time_start": 485655, "question": "63+97+557", "correct_answer": 717, "events": [["calc_6", 488290], ["calc_3", 488728], ["calc_+", 489037], ["calc_9", 489601], ["calc_7", 489920], ["calc_+", 490348], ["calc_5", 490663], ["calc_5", 490773], ["calc_7", 491007], ["calc_=", 491446], ["submit", 494276]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "154", "answered_time": 494276, "user_answer": "717", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "154", "question_time_start": 494277, "question": "7+4+4+48", "correct_answer": 63, "events": [["submit", 499504]], "time_left_end": "149", "answered_time": 499504, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 9, "start_time": 499504, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "149", "question_time_start": 499504, "question": "39+99+23+96", "correct_answer": 257, "events": [["calc_3", 502074], ["calc_9", 502437], ["calc_+", 502762], ["calc_9", 503070], ["calc_9", 503209], ["calc_+", 503770], ["calc_2", 504141], ["calc_3", 504357], ["calc_+", 504820], ["calc_9", 505325], ["calc_6", 505586], ["calc_=", 505900], ["submit", 508577]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "140", "answered_time": 508577, "user_answer": "257", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "140", "question_time_start": 508578, "question": "4+3+8+66", "correct_answer": 81, "events": [["submit", 517118]], "time_left_end": "132", "answered_time": 517118, "user_answer": "81", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "132", "question_time_start": 517119, "question": "34+96+336", "correct_answer": 466, "events": [["submit", 527483]], "time_left_end": "121", "answered_time": 527483, "user_answer": "466", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "121", "question_time_start": 527483, "question": "44+64+26+28", "correct_answer": 162, "events": [["submit", 536243]], "time_left_end": "113", "answered_time": 536243, "user_answer": "162", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "113", "question_time_start": 536244, "question": "8+33+26", "correct_answer": 67, "events": [["submit", 540136]], "time_left_end": "109", "answered_time": 540136, "user_answer": "67", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "109", "question_time_start": 540137, "question": "6+39+99", "correct_answer": 144, "events": [["submit", 543428]], "time_left_end": "105", "answered_time": 543428, "user_answer": "144", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "105", "question_time_start": 543428, "question": "23+948", "correct_answer": 971, "events": [["submit", 548203]], "time_left_end": "101", "answered_time": 548203, "user_answer": "971", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "101", "question_time_start": 548204, "question": "37+329", "correct_answer": 366, "events": [["submit", 554820]], "time_left_end": "94", "answered_time": 554820, "user_answer": "366", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "94", "question_time_start": 554820, "question": "19+936", "correct_answer": 955, "events": [["submit", 558401]], "time_left_end": "90", "answered_time": 558401, "user_answer": "955", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "90", "question_time_start": 558401, "question": "3+3+7+54", "correct_answer": 67, "events": [["submit", 562960]], "time_left_end": "86", "answered_time": 562960, "user_answer": "67", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 9, "start_time": 562960, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "86", "question_time_start": 562960, "question": "9+77+88", "correct_answer": 174, "events": [["submit", 574764]], "time_left_end": "74", "answered_time": 574764, "user_answer": "174", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "74", "question_time_start": 574765, "question": "18+556", "correct_answer": 574, "events": [["submit", 579437]], "time_left_end": "69", "answered_time": 579437, "user_answer": "574", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "69", "question_time_start": 579437, "question": "98+568", "correct_answer": 666, "events": [["submit", 583722]], "time_left_end": "65", "answered_time": 583722, "user_answer": "666", "user_correct": "True", "score": "29"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "65", "question_time_start": 583723, "question": "74+83+73+67", "correct_answer": 297, "events": [["calc_7", 587245], ["calc_4", 587438], ["calc_+", 587895], ["calc_8", 588431], ["calc_3", 588764], ["calc_+", 589321], ["calc_7", 589826], ["calc_3", 590208], ["calc_+", 590640], ["calc_6", 591140], ["calc_7", 591545], ["calc_=", 591877], ["submit", 594347]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "54", "answered_time": 594346, "user_answer": "297", "user_correct": "True", "score": "30"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "54", "question_time_start": 594347, "question": "9+8+4+79", "correct_answer": 100, "events": [["submit", 598766]], "time_left_end": "50", "answered_time": 598766, "user_answer": "100", "user_correct": "True", "score": "31"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "50", "question_time_start": 598766, "question": "79+98+67+19", "correct_answer": 263, "events": [["calc_1", 613095], ["calc_9", 613773], ["calc_6", 613928], ["calc_+", 614267], ["calc_6", 614661], ["calc_7", 614921], ["calc_=", 615264], ["submit", 617584]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "31", "answered_time": 617584, "user_answer": "263", "user_correct": "True", "score": "32"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "31", "question_time_start": 617585, "question": "48+53+277", "correct_answer": 378, "events": [["submit", 623777]], "time_left_end": "25", "answered_time": 623777, "user_answer": "378", "user_correct": "True", "score": "33"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "25", "question_time_start": 623778, "question": "69+718", "correct_answer": 787, "events": [["calc_6", 628625], ["calc_9", 629415], ["calc_+", 629973], ["calc_7", 630402], ["calc_1", 630709], ["calc_8", 631106], ["calc_=", 631435], ["submit", 634101]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "15", "answered_time": 634101, "user_answer": "787", "user_correct": "True", "score": "34"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "15", "question_time_start": 634102, "question": "4+69+69", "correct_answer": 142, "events": [["submit", 639285]], "time_left_end": "9", "answered_time": 639285, "user_answer": "142", "user_correct": "True", "score": "35"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "9", "question_time_start": 639286, "question": "8+8+8+93", "correct_answer": 117, "events": [["submit", 642941]], "time_left_end": "6", "answered_time": 642941, "user_answer": "117", "user_correct": "True", "score": "36"}}}, "block_4": {"mean_level": 9, "start_time": 642942, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "6", "question_time_start": 642942, "question": "4+6+4+48", "correct_answer": 62, "events": [["submit", 647182]], "time_left_end": "2", "answered_time": 647182, "user_answer": "64", "user_correct": "False", "score": "35"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "2", "question_time_start": 647182, "question": "86+68+77+68", "correct_answer": 299, "events": []}}}}}